http://www.weathertech.com/service/privacy/

Skip to Main Content
$
Privacy Policy
WEATHERTECH DIRECT, LLC PRIVACY POLICY - EFFECTIVE 1/1/2020
We value you as a customer and take your privacy seriously and we want you to know how we collect, use, share and
protect your information.
This Privacy Policy tells you:
What information we collect
How we use that information
How we may share that information
Your choices regarding your personal information
This Privacy Policy applies to WeatherTech Direct, LLC and any of its affiliated entities ("WeatherTech"),
www.weathertech.com (the "Site") and information or pages found
therein. Our Conditions and Terms of Use govern this Privacy Policy. To the extent there is a conflict between the
terms of this Privacy Policy and the Conditions and Terms of Use, the Conditions and Terms of Use shall govern.
If you visit or shop at the Site, you accept and agree to be bound
by our Conditions and Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. Please read them carefully. If you do not agree, please
do not visit or use the Site.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We collect customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about
our products, services, contests, and promotions, and that we believe is necessary to administer our business.
WeatherTech recognizes that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly. We collect information such
as your name, email address, mailing address, and phone and credit card numbers that you provide when you begin the
checkout process by entering your email address, place an order, join our mailing list, register with us or
participate in a contest, promotion or survey. We also may collect information that we deem necessary to maintain
and administer your account with WeatherTech. We also maintain a record of your product interests and your purchases
online or in our retail store location. We may also collect information you give us about other people, such as the
name and address of a gift recipient, or the name and contact info of a third party to receive any of our products
or services. We may also collect information we receive about you from other sources, including third parties that
help us update, expand and analyze our records and identify new customers.
AGGREGATE AND ANONYMOUS DATA
Aggregate and anonymous data ("AA Data") are information collected automatically through the operation of
the Site. We may collect usage data (such as which website pages you visit with us and in what sequence) through the
use of various technologies. For example, we may collect IP addresses from individuals who visit the Site. An IP
address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Internet.
Internet servers, the computers that "serve up" web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP
address. We do not link IP addresses to any Personal Information, so although your session may be logged, you will
remain anonymous to us. We may also collect password information from you when you log in, as well as computer and
connection information such as browser type or version. During some visits, we may use software tools, such as
Javascript, to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, time spent
on certain pages, page interaction information, and methods used to browse away from the page.
USE OF COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES
Like many websites, we use "cookies" or other similar technologies to collect AA Data. A cookie is a small
data file that writes to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit the website. Cookies allow the
website to measure traffic activity on the website and to improve your user experience, for example, by remembering
your passwords and viewing preferences, allowing you to visit restricted portions of the site, and tracking the
progress and number of entries in activities that require registration or entry, such as sweepstakes, promotions,
sales and contests. Similarly, if you have asked us to send you information about upcoming products and promotions,
using cookies we collect information about which website pages you have visited and in what order ("Clickstream
Data") that may allow us to narrow or limit the materials provided to you based on your prior online activities
or preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to
refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent, but it is possible that some parts of the Site will not
function properly if you do so. In addition, we may use a service that collects data remotely by using so-called
"pixel tags" "web beacons" clear GIFs" or similar means (collectively "Pixel
Tags") embedded in the Site’s content. A Pixel Tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel (1 x 1)
that is ordinarily not visible to website visitors and may be associated with cookies on the visitors’ hard
drives. This information is AA Data.
HOW WE USE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU
We use customer personal information to provide accurate services and to advise our valued customers of promotions
that may be of interest to them. WeatherTech does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third
parties. We may share your information with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as: fulfilling
orders, delivering packages, sending WeatherTech marketing materials, fulfilling subscription services, conducting
research and analysis, handling and processing credit card payments. We may disclose your personal information to
trusted third parties whom we engage to process your personal information for us. We may disclose personal
information with other companies and organizations for fraud and credit risk purposes. We may disclose your personal
information to third parties with regard to the analysis and support of your use of the Site. We may be required to
share personal information in response to a regulation, court order or subpoena or discovery request. We may also
share information to respond to a government request or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to
protect the rights, property or safety of WeatherTech, our customers, or others; to prevent harm or loss; or in
connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity.
We may also share personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar
event. We may share personal information in connection with financial products or services related to our business
such as private label credit cards. We also may share personal information in connection with co-branded products or
service offerings. For example, if we were to offer a WeatherTech credit card, during the application process we may
share your personal information with our banking partners that issue any such card.
THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING AND LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
The Site may contain links to other sites or contain third-party advertising. These third parties’ websites and
advertisers, or the internet advertising companies that work on their behalf, may use technology to send (or
"serve") the advertisements that appear on the Site directly to your browser. They automatically receive
your IP address when this happens. They also automatically receive and record information from your computer and
browser, including your cookie information. They may also use cookies, Javascript, Pixel Tags and other technologies
to deliver advertisements, collect information about the effectiveness of their advertisements, and to collect
anonymous information about your visits to the Site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad or to
customize the advertising content you see (but not your name, address or other personal information). The third
parties’ use of their own cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. For information about these
specialized cookies and other technologies, and how to "opt out" of information collection by these
companies, we suggest you visit https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads or http://networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp
Please be aware that the Site may contain links to other sites that will not follow the same Privacy Policy as
WeatherTech. Clicking on an advertisement or on links or other elements on the website may take you to an entirely
different website. These websites may send their own cookies to you and may collect data and make use of that data
in ways that WeatherTech would not. Once you have left the Site, this Privacy Policy will no longer apply to any
personal information or any other data collected from or provided by you. You should review the applicable privacy
policy to determine how that other website will handle such data.
DATA SECURITY DISCLAIMER
WeatherTech takes reasonable security precautions to secure the personal information that you choose to provide us
against loss, misuse, alteration or unauthorized access of such information. Unfortunately, no transmission of data
over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control
of WeatherTech to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect
your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal information you transmit to us.
Any such transmission is done at your own risk.
CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request
personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we
become aware that a user is under the age of 13 and has registered with WeatherTech without prior verifiable
parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable information from our files. Please note that we
nevertheless maintain a record of that person’s name and address in a "do not register" file to
avoid subsequent registration by a child under the age of 13. By using this website you agree to respond truthfully
and accurately about your age. Children under the age of 13 years are expressly prohibited from submitting or
providing any personal information on the Site.
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
Please visit our supplemental privacy page for California consumers here
NEVADA PRIVACY RIGHTS
Nevada consumers can request that we do not sell any covered information that we have collected or will collect by
emailing consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com. Please
include name, address, and email in the request. Expect a reply within 60 days after sending a verified request.
USER CONSENT
By providing any personal information to WeatherTech, all users, including, without limitation, users in all foreign
countries, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of such personal
information across international borders in accordance with WeatherTech standard operations, including the
collection, storage and processing of such information in the United States of America.
CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY
WeatherTech may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review the Privacy Policy periodically. Each and
any version and subsequent update of this Privacy Policy can also be printed for your records upon your review. You
should periodically review this Privacy Policy because by agreeing to visit the Site you agree to accept and be
bound by any such changes that we make to the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, then please do not visit the
Site. Except as otherwise mentioned herein, the Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information
we collect from you on the Site..
QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND YOUR CHOICES
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or have any objections to this Privacy Policy,
please contact us directly and direct your inquiries to our Customer Service Department at:
WeatherTech Direct, LLC
841 Remington Blvd.
Bolingbrook, IL 60440
(800) 900-8260
You may choose to stop receiving marketing or promotional emails, direct mail, phone and mobile marketing
communications, update and correct your personal information, cancel your account or request that we no longer use
your personal information to provide you services. To accomplish any of the requests, please contact us at the
contact information given above and ask for our Customer Service department.
+
Customer Service
Orders
Track My Order Return Policy Shipping Policy Gift Card Balance My Account Product Return Form Curbside Order Pickup
Products
View All Products Lifetime Limited Warranty New Product Updates Special Offers Consumer Alert: Unauthorized Dealers
General Info
Company Info Factory Store Info FAQs Newsletter Sign Up WeatherTech Blog Careers Terms of Use Privacy Policy Biometric Information Privacy Act Policy Trademark Usage Website Accessibility
You are now leaving WeatherTech.com and will be directed to
Close
